(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
はろーぼ飯店へようこそ
Welcome to Harobo Restaurant
with Ø / 作詞・作曲・編曲：K's
with Ø / Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: K's
君の心の 中を全部見せてよ
Show me everything inside your heart.
何が好きで何が嫌いで 僕はどのくらいかな
What do you like, what do you hate, and how do I measure up?
今日はどんな服着て どこで何をしてるの
What are you wearing today, where are you, and what are you doing?
全部全部隠さないでいいよ 僕に教えて
You don't have to hide anything. Tell me everything.
経験なんて気にしない
I don't care about experience.
偏見バカバカだらない
Prejudice is just plain stupid.
期待しないなんて嘘ばかり
Saying you don't expect anything is just a pack of lies.
顔色伺いギリギリに
Barely scraping by while reading the room.
一人で踊ればいい
You might as well just dance alone.
...眠れない
...I can't sleep
ずっと欲しかった言葉も
Even the words I've always wanted
しらふのままじゃ出てこないんだら
Won't come out if I stay sober
三つ数えて
Count to three
世界が止まれば
And if the world would stop
いいのに
It would be nice
元に戻れない
Can't go back
触れて溶けあうくらいの距離感で
At a distance where we touch and melt together
僕のことだけ見ててよ
Look only at me
跡つけてよ 消えないくらいに
Leave a mark so it won't disappear
ほらね、今ギュッとして
See, hold me tight now
曖昧だっていいよなんて
Saying it's okay even if it's vague
僕はわかるから
Because I understand
気づかないフリしてあげるってだからね
I'll pretend not to notice, so you see
今好きって言ってよ
Tell me you love me now
好きって言ってよ
Tell me you love me
永遠なんてありゃしない
There's no such thing as forever
健全なんておそばかり
Wholesomeness is all a lie
期待したいなんて傲慢ばかり
Wanting to hope is just arrogance
顔色伺うのもギリギリ
Looking at your face is barely manageable
一人で泣けばいい
I should just cry alone
でも一人じゃ笑えない
But I can't laugh alone
ずっと欲しかった言葉も
Even the words I've always wanted
思ったままじゃ出てこないんだら
Won't come out as I think them
三つ数えて
Count to three
世界が変われば
And if the world would change
いいのに
It would be nice
元に戻れない
Can't go back
ガラガラと音立てて崩れる
Collapsing with a clatter
景色の中落ちていく
Falling through the scenery
見つけ出してよ 離れないくらいに
Find me so we won't be apart
ほらね、今ギュッとして
See, hold me tight now
何回だっていいよなんて
Saying as many times is okay
僕はわかるから
Because I understand
いつか最後に聞かせてくれるってだからね
Because you'll let me hear it one last time someday
また好きって言ってよ
Tell me you love me again
夜が明けるまで
Until the night breaks
話を聞いて
Listen to me
終わらない夢みたいに輝いて見えた
It looked shining like an endless dream
どうか今だけ消さないで
Please don't erase it just for now
冗談じゃないよ
It's not a joke
君のいない明日なんて全部いらない
I don't need any tomorrow without you
ずっと一緒だよね
We'll always be together, right?
触れて溶けあうくらいの距離感で
At a distance where we touch and melt together
僕のことだけ見ててよ
Look only at me
跡つけてよ 消えないくらいに
Leave a mark so it won't disappear
ほらね、今ギュッとして
See, hold me tight now
何回だっていいよなんて
Saying as many times is okay
僕はわかるから
Because I understand
気づかないフリしてあげるってだからね
I'll pretend not to notice, so you see
今好きって言ってよ
Tell me you love me now
好きって言ってよ
Tell me you love me
ないない
Nothing nothing
ないない 会のない
Nothing, nothing, no meeting
深い崖ばかり
Only deep cliffs
愛のない 答え
Answers with no love
堂々巡り
Going in circles
自分不在 どこにもいない
No self, not anywhere
ないじゃない
There is nothing, right?
あいまいな愛
Vague love
色のない愛
Colorless love
擬態 以外
Other than mimicry
独り言みたい
Like a monologue
おかげさまで どちら様
Thanks to you, who are you?
ご退散様々
Farewell in various ways
何者でもないまま
Remaining as no one
何もできないまま
Remaining unable to do anything
生きるのは無駄ですが 悪いことですが
Living is a waste, it's a bad thing, but...
ここにいない いない いないのは
What isn't here, isn't here, isn't here
自分 自分
Is myself, myself
誰も見ない 見ない 見ないまま
Without anyone looking, looking, looking
吐き捨ててサヨナラ
Spitting it out, goodbye
嬉しくない 悲しくもない
I'm not happy, nor am I sad
透明な気分
A transparent feeling
足りない自分 合わす顔もない
My insufficient self, no face to show
ない
Nothing
笑えないじゃない
Can't laugh, can I?
愛じゃない 曖昧
Not love, vague
閉じたままがいい
Better to stay closed
変わり映えしない
Nothing changes
期待だけ大
Only expectations are high
嫌々投げ出された際
When thrown out reluctantly
てめえは知らない
You don't know
ここにいたい いたい いたいのも
What wants to stay here, stay here, stay here
自分 自分
Is myself, myself
味は苦い 苦い 苦いのに
Even though the taste is bitter, bitter, bitter
誰も見ない 見ない 見ないまま 吐き捨てて さようなら
No one looks, looks, stays looking away, spitting it out, goodbye
帰れない 行く先もない 迷子ならいっそ
Can't go home, nowhere to go, if I'm lost, then just...
迷路を築 間違えてない
Building a maze, I haven't made a mistake
まだ分からない
I still don't know
ない どうだっていいじゃない
Nothing. It doesn't matter anyway.
Lo lo lo...
I don't need stars, I don't need stars
Just no more stars, I don't need stars, just no more stars
名前も形も いっそ失くしてしまえばいい
Names and shapes, it's better to just lose them all
またハイ ひとつひとつから始めればいい
Then, hi, just start again, one by one
ここにいない いない いないのは 自分 自分
The one who is not here, not here, not here is me, me
誰も見ない 見ない 見ないまま 吐き捨てて さようなら
No one looks, looks, stays looking away, spitting it out, goodbye
嬉しいくらい 悲しくもない 飛べない気分
So happy it's almost sad, I feel like I can't fly
足りない自分 合わす顔もない
My lacking self, I have no face to show
ない ない ないままで ここにいたい いたい
Nothing, nothing, just as it is, I want to stay here, stay here
笑いたいじゃない
Don't I want to laugh?
はーい！というわけで聞いてくれてありがとう！
Hi! So, thank you for listening!
改めまして、ハロローボ！ホロライブ所属0期生
Once again, Hello-robo! Hololive 0th Generation,
バーチャル高性能ロボットの、ロボ子だよー！
High-performance virtual robot, Roboco!
今日は僕の誕生日ライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to my birthday live today!
もう高性能？みたいなコメント拾わないからね、だってもう今日9歳！
I won't be picking up comments like "High performance?" anymore, 'cause I'm 9 years old today!
主役！あ、やべ、誕生日のお答え質問しようと思ったのに言っちゃったｗ
The star! Ah, shoot, I was going to ask a question about my birthday, but I just said it lol.
はい、そう、ロボ子なんと今年で9歳になりました！9歳！
Yes, that's right, Roboco has actually turned 9 this year! 9 years old!
ヤバない？来年もう二桁になる。ヤバい、ヤバすぎる、ワクワクしてきた。
Isn't that crazy? Next year I'll be in double digits. It's crazy, too crazy, I'm getting excited.
最後の一桁、楽しんでいきたいと思います！はい、というわけで
I want to enjoy my last single-digit year! Alright, so,
本日のハッシュタグを紹介します！
I'll introduce today's hashtag!
ジョジョン！本日のハッシュタグは…あ、こっちだった。
Ta-da! Today's hashtag is... oh, it was this way.
#ロボ子爆誕2025 ですね！皆さん見えましたか？
It's #RobocoExplosion2025! Did everyone see it?
きっと高性能な君たちだったら、もう #ロボ子爆誕2025 をつけて
If you're high-performance fans, you're probably already
呟いていることでしょう。はい！
tweeting with #RobocoExplosion2025. Yes!
たくさん僕の可愛いスクショと共に、ポストしてってくださいね。
Please keep posting with lots of cute screenshots of me.
こうして人は循環してくんですよ。ポスト！ｗ
This is how people circulate. Post! lol
はい、というわけで、まずは今日はね、僕のオリジナル曲「With Love」から始まって「ないない」を歌ったんですけど
Alright, so first off today, we started with my original song "With Love" and then I sang "Nainai".
うん、どうでしたか？
Yeah, how was it?
With Love、With Love MVと同じね、ウルフカットじゃなくて
For "With Love," just like in the MV, I went with my usual
通常の強そうなロングのやつで巻き巻きでいったんですけど
strong-looking long hair, all curled up, instead of the wolf cut.
え、どうだった？良かった？
So, how was it? Was it good?
え、そう、なんかもう久々だよね。この…このナイティドレスとかも。
Yeah, it's been a while, hasn't it? This... this nightie dress and all.
ウルフカットなんて初めてなんじゃない？
And maybe it's the first time for the wolf cut?
ショートカット。ショート動画でしか撮らないからね。ふふ、セクシーでしょ？
The short cut. I only do it for short videos. Hehe, sexy, right?
そして！
And!
ステージがなんか、すっごいかっこいい！え、かっこよすぎる！
The stage is like, so cool! Whoa, it's way too cool!
ふぉ〜、今回はこんな感じなんですね。
Whoa, so this is what it's like this time.
今日はなんか色々楽しみなことがいっぱいありそうだけど、
It seems like there's going to be a lot of fun things today, but,
え、一体なんで今日このステージなんだろうなー？
I wonder why the stage is like this today?
うーん、なんと後でね…
Hmm, and actually, later...
ロボサがいるらしいんですけれども
I hear there's a Robosa here...
コメントにいないロボサがいるらしくてですね
Apparently, there's a Robosa in the comments who isn't usually there.
気になった方は探してみてくださいね
If you're curious, please try looking for them.
いるかな？
Are they here?
あれ、ロボサいるかなー？
Oh, I wonder where Robosa is?
あれー、いるかなー？
Hmm, I wonder if they're there?
きっと目...見つけてる人多い
I'm sure... many of you have already found them.
正解
Correct.
ここにいまーす！
They're right here!
特等席！
A special seat!
お前はいったい誰なんだー！
Who on earth are you?!
ずっと僕のことリハ中も見守っててくれてます
They've been watching over me even during rehearsals.
ロボサかわちいいね
Robosa is so cute.
はい、というわけで今日は誕生日のために
Anyway, for my birthday today...
いっぱい、いっぱい、みんな、そして僕が楽しめる
I've prepared many, many songs that you and I...
歌をたくさんね、ご用意いたしましたので
...can all enjoy together.
いっぱいレッスンもしたので楽しんでってください！
I've practiced a lot, so please enjoy!
はい、この後はそろそろ一人でも歌うと思うんだけど
Well, I'll be singing alone for a bit, but...
ゲストも呼んでって歌っちゃおうかなと思います
...I'm also planning to invite some guests to sing with me.
最初はこちらだろうなー？
I wonder who the first one will be?
Who could it be?
なんか、すっごいキスいっぱいしたい気分になってきた
Suddenly, I feel like giving lots of kisses.
なんでだろ、なんでだ
I wonder why... why is that?
チュッチュッチュッ...
Mwah mwah mwah...
モエチャッカファイア
Moe Chakka Fire
よくぞ御心に沿ったご主人様
Welcome, Master, just as you desired.
そのお隣座った、せーの！
Now sit beside me, on three!
萌え萌え萌え萌え！
Moe moe moe moe!
この辺で誰が喜ぶのさ
Who's going to be happy with this?
ねえ教えて笑顔でアップップ
Tell me, keep a straight face.
愛想を振るってご苦労様
Thanks for the hard work, being so charming.
あたしとあなた、せーの！
You and me, on three!
だっだっだっ！
Da da da!
この辺で誰が喜ぶのさ
Who's going to be happy with this?
ねえ教えて笑顔でアップップ
Tell me, keep a straight face.
ヒラリハラリ女の子
Fluttering, fluttering girl.
フワリフワリ言葉の層
Softly, softly, layers of words.
それってつまり幼い子
In other words, a childish one.
感情的リアル笑顔でアップップ
Emotional and real, keep a straight face.
人は見かけによらぬもの
You can't judge a person by their looks.
嘘嘘だと見抜けばいい
You should see through the lies.
地道な顔して袖裾の皮
A steady face, the edge of the sleeve.
アパレハ、サメハダ、アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Apareha, samehada, un, deux, trois.
間違ったご神名をいただきます
I'll take that incorrect divine name.
あたしとあなた、せーの！
You and me, on three!
だっだっだっ！
Da da da!
これは勝手に、お疲れ様
Taking it upon myself, good job.
遊びましょう笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, keep a straight face.
ヒラリハラリ、ここはどこ
Fluttering, fluttering, where am I?
フワリフワリ、外れましょう
Softly, softly, let's deviate.
それってつまり幼い子
In other words, a childish one.
感情的リアル笑顔でアップップ
Emotional and real, keep a straight face.
歌い出す、秘密の鐘
The secret bell begins to ring.
終わることのないこの世界
This world that never ends.
悲しい子供は、虚しい子供は
A sad child, a hollow child...
眠らせて
Let them sleep.
甘い誠遊びましょう笑顔でアップップ
Sweet truth, let's play, keep a straight face.
ヒラリハラリ女の子
Fluttering, fluttering girl.
フワリフワリ言葉の層
Softly, softly, layers of words.
それってつまり幼い子
In other words, a childish one.
感情的リアル笑顔でアップップ
Emotional and real, keep a straight face.
遊びましょう笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, keep a straight face.
笑顔でアップップ
Keep a straight face.
G4L
あれが世界なんて
If that's the world...
誰のなれの果て
A shadow of whose former self?
答えも本心も異語でこれだけ
Answers and true feelings, only this in a foreign tongue.
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
No use worrying about it, right?
あれは夢だったって思うことより下って
Lower than thinking it was all a dream.
次々何も無いけど助けてよフォローワー
One thing after another, but there's nothing, help me followers.
できるだけ、お任せに負け
As much as possible, losing to fate.
残す場残す場ラキラキ
Leave a place, leave a place, lucky lucky.
アリよ割り切ったらさオリよ
Accepting it, then it's done.
割り切れたらさー
If we could just divide it up...
オリオン たくなのになのにとか フフ
Orion, despite it all, despite it all, haha
もうやだ あーあーあー
I've had enough, ahh, ahh, ahh
万事神聖快か
Is everything sacred and pleasant?
安泰外は 安泰外は いらないないない
Outside is safe, outside is safe, I don't need it at all
張らないでバリア
Don't put up a barrier
有るはずのナニカ あったならばハッピージャンピングヤ
If that 'something' that should exist was there, happy jumping, yeah
案ずるなその手と 案ずるなこの手を
Don't worry about those hands, don't worry about these hands
繋いだら無理にちょっと放さないわ
Once we're connected, I won't let go for anything
案ずるなその手が 案ずるなこの手を
Don't worry about those hands, don't worry about these hands
掴んだらゴミ処理を My Love
Once you grab hold, take out the trash, My Love
これで終わりなんて
Thinking this is the end...
I gotta remind myself なんて
I gotta remind myself or whatever
脳内がバグって 願って 願ってね
My brain is bugging out, wishing and praying
エスケープしたい自意識ちゃん
My little self-consciousness wants to escape
なにもかも満点 ピーキンペンペン
Everything's perfect, peaking pain-pain
痛いのバイバイ Everyday
Say bye-bye to the pain, everyday
迷うてけるけどラブルベナスのんで関係ない
I might get lost, but I'll drink love and venus, so it's fine
慣れより猫 拙いも結構 足は足だ見といてよ Lady
Cats over habits, being clumsy is fine, feet are feet, watch me, Lady
もう今日で終わらせたいなって
Thinking I want to end it all today
リスタートできたらって
Wishing I could just restart
でも無理よもう
But it's impossible now
What's your mind?
アディオス 割り切れたらさー
Adios, if we could just divide it up...
オリオン たくなのになのにとか フフ
Orion, despite it all, despite it all, haha
もうやだ あーあーあー
I've had enough, ahh, ahh, ahh
万事神聖快か
Is everything sacred and pleasant?
安泰外は 安泰外は いらないないない
Outside is safe, outside is safe, I don't need it at all
張らないでバリア
Don't put up a barrier
有るはずのナニカ あったならばハッピージャンピングヤ
If that 'something' that should exist was there, happy jumping, yeah
案ずるなその手と 案ずるなこの手を
Don't worry about those hands, don't worry about these hands
繋いだら無理にちょっと放さないわ
Once we're connected, I won't let go for anything
案ずるなその手が 案ずるなこの手を
Don't worry about those hands, don't worry about these hands
掴んだらゴミ処理を My Love
Once you grab hold, take out the trash, My Love
ゴミ処理を My Love
Take out the trash, My Love
半端なら K.O.
If you're half-baked, it's a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to feel lightheaded, go ahead
開演準備しちゃおうか
Shall we get ready for the show?
泣いても笑っても愛してね
Love me whether I cry or laugh
ほら正解だ 手を響かせろ
See, that's the right answer, let your hands ring out
踊 作詞：DECO*27 作曲：Giga, TeddyLoid
Odo | Lyrics: DECO*27 | Composition: Giga, TeddyLoid
なんだかなってつまんないこともありますでしょう
I'm sure there are times when things just feel dull
ノリノリなの？ハンディハンディだっそ
Are you feeling it? Handy handy dash out
夜なちょっとドローに パッと放っただろうが
In the dead of night, you let it out in a flash, didn't you?
怒れど落ちて エーイ
Get angry, fall down, ayyy
そろそろ行ってもっと頑張って 踊るまでもっと頑張って
It's about time, try harder, try harder until you dance
繋ごう一人より二人 増えたらあし心配ないや
Let's connect, two is better than one, if we increase, no need to worry
Alright 任せて Don’t mind 涙になんだえみんなでわっちゃいな
Alright, leave it to me, don't mind, let's all get wild with our tears
案外サクッといっちゃいそう
Seems like it might go unexpectedly smoothly
半端なら K.O.
If you're half-baked, it's a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to feel lightheaded, go ahead
開演準備しちゃおうか
Shall we get ready for the show?
泣いても笑っても愛してね
Love me whether I cry or laugh
ほら正解だ 手を響かせろ
See, that's the right answer, let your hands ring out
今夜はアッパーバディ
Tonight we're upper-body
踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独さえ巻きおこせ
Start dancing, start dancing, whip up even loneliness
痛みまで お裾分け ここらでバイバイレッゴー
Share even the pain, say bye-bye here and let's go
どんな毒だと言ったって 今日の化粧盤では
No matter what kind of poison it is, on today's stage...
最高で突っ込んで しまっちゃうでしょう Oh yeah
You'll plunge in with the best, won't you? Oh yeah
アッパーなテンションで 参っちゃってんのさとお
With this upper-bound tension, you're totally done for
ドパッと吹き出すのは 本音の独り言
What gushes out is a monologue of your true feelings
別に興味ない どこに関係ない
I'm not interested, it's irrelevant where
塞ぎ込んで絶不調
Shutting down, in a total slump
合図を奏でて パッパッパッパッヤー
Play the signal, pa-pa-pa-pa-ya
ほら集まって 弥栄だ
Look, gather round, it's a celebration
泣いていこうか
Let's cry it out
半端なら K.O.!
If you're half-hearted, it's a K.O.!
Ye-Ye-Ye-Ye-Ye-Yeah!
踊りなせよ 踊りなせよ 鼓動咲き舞い踊れ
Keep on dancing, keep on dancing! Let your heart skip a beat and dance away!
傷みまで 押し上げ 今宵もあっぱれだ
Pushing even the pain aside, tonight is truly splendid!
またのお越しを いざ問おう
Come again soon, I shall ask you then!
次会うまで お元気で ここらでバイバイレジャー
Stay well until we meet again, so long for now!
やあ、おっ魂消てるその兄ちゃん 何か辛いことあったんか？ 俺でよけりゃ話してくんない 力になるぜ
Hey there, you look like you've seen a ghost. Did something bad happen? If you're okay with me, why not talk about it? I'll help you out.
一体 どんなことがあった？ それ聞いて話して兄弟 これをやるから元気出しな 金ならまた今度でいいさ
What on earth happened? Tell me all about it, brother. Take this and cheer up. You can pay me back some other time.
シャンティ シャンティ シャンティ シャンティ ハッピー キャンディ ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー キャンディ メニーメニーマネー
Shanti, shanti, shanti, shanti, happy candy! Happy, happy, happy candy! Many, many money!
眠らない夜のチャイナダンスは すべてがカーニバル どうにかなりゃあいいが 付き合って終わった吸ってたい
This sleepless night of China dance is a total carnival. Hope it all works out. I just want to stick with it until the end.
今夜も来たのかい お気に召したかい 代価はこれくらい？ え？ え？ え？
Did you come back tonight? Did you like it? Is this much the price? Eh? Eh? Eh?
払えないのかい ならばしょうがない 君にぴったりの仕事があるから こっちについてきな
Can't pay up? Well, that's a shame. I have a job that's perfect for you, so come with me.
こっちについてきな
Come with me.
汚れちまった羽が剥がれた女 喋れた看板掲げた女 多寡が舞い触れた容赦 端からあいつの思惑通りだ
A woman with soiled, torn wings. A woman who put up a talkative sign. A mercy touched by many dances. It's been his plan from the start.
気狂ってるめ三拍子 散るってもう納得 蝶々 飛んで 凛道 咲かせた果て 盲信の神 お金にたまえ
A crazy triple meter, I'm already convinced. Butterflies fly, gentians bloom. A god of blind faith, give us money.
黙れ 座れ 黙れや 殴れ 殴れ 殴れや 縛れ 縛れ 縛れや
Shut up, sit down, just shut up! Strike, strike, just strike! Bind, bind, just bind!
バラせ バラせ バラせや バラせ バラせ バラせや バラせ バラせ バラせや
Expose, expose, just expose! Expose, expose, just expose! Expose, expose, just expose!
今夜の味はどうだい お気に召したかい 代価はこれくらい？
How does it taste tonight? Did you like it? Is this much the price?
生きてりゃお客 死んでりゃ商材 卒なくまみれろ 転がせビジネス どっちを向いてんだ
Alive, you're a customer; dead, you're merchandise. Get flawlessly covered in it. Let the business roll. Which way are you looking?
どっちを向いてんだ
Which way are you looking?
やあ、おっ魂消てるそのお嬢ちゃん
Hey there, you look like you've seen a ghost, young lady.
俺でよけりゃ話してくんない
If you're okay with me, why not talk about it?
はーい！というわけで、
Hi! So, as you can see...
かっこいいでしょ？
I look cool, right?
はい！こちらがロボ子の新衣装となります！
Yes! This is Roboco's new outfit!
見て、下から！超かっこいいの！どやあ。
Look from below! It's so cool! Ta-da.
え、サングラス似合いすぎでは？
Wait, don't these sunglasses look too good on me?
やばい、みんなが恋しちゃう。
Oh no, everyone's going to fall in love with me.
俺に惚れると火傷するぜ。
If you fall for me, you'll get burned.
やべー草すぎ、あはははは！
That was way too cringy, LOL!
笑わないでー。笑うのやめてー。うっ、おっほん。
Don't laugh! Stop laughing! Ugh, ahem.
はい、というわけで、
Alright, as I was saying...
見て、これ、かっこいいでしょ？
Look at this, isn't it cool?
なんかさ、指についてんだけど。
There's something on my finger, though.
まだよく見えないね。
You can't really see it yet.
まだ、まだよく見えないね。
Still... you still can't really see it.
え、踊の時に、カラーライズ衣装からチェンジしたんだけど、
So, I changed from the colorized outfit during 'Odo'...
チェンジした瞬間、ちゃんとみんな分かった？
Did you all notice the exact moment I changed?
湧いてきました？
Are you getting hyped?
一瞬だったでしょう。うふふ。
It was just for a moment, wasn't it? Ufufu.
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
可愛い。カッコイイ。ね。
Cute. Cool. Right?
これなんか両方あるよね。カッコイイし可愛いよね。
This has both, doesn't it? Cool and cute.
プリティーでクールなの子、これ。
Pretty and cool. This outfit.
いっぱい見て、いっぱい見て。
Take a good look, take a good look.
足からちょっと見ていく？
Shall we start looking from the feet?
お、見て。え、やばい。
Oh, look. Wow, amazing.
カッコよすぎるんだが。
It's way too cool.
見て、これロボット特有のさ、この...
Look, this is unique to robots, this...
これ人間だったら多分めっちゃ歩きづらいんじゃ...
If you were human, this would probably be hard to walk in...
みんな多分歩けないよね、この靴。
Everyone probably couldn't walk in these shoes.
僕、歩けるんだけどさ。ふふふ。
I can walk in them, though. Fufufu.
おー。
Oh.
ね、この靴で多分僕走ったら、多分めっちゃ...
Right, if I probably ran in these shoes, I'd probably...
倍コケると思うから、歩きます。
Fall over twice as much, so I'll walk.
どう？どう？どう？
How is it? How is it? How is it?
はい。そして上からね。
Yes. And from the top.
カッコよく決まって、ベルト。
Set coolly, the belt.
あればあるだけいいですから。
The more of them, the better.
いっぱいつけてもらえました。
I got to wear a lot.
今回マジで装飾品もね、カッコイイ。
The accessories are seriously cool this time too.
キラキラ。
Sparkly.
金色ネックレス。
Gold necklace.
これダイヤとかカミナリがついてるのかな？うん。
Does this have diamonds or lightning on it? Yeah.
あと、なんか姿がちょっとおかしくなってるけど。
Also, my appearance is a bit strange.
僕の新衣装に合わせて、ロボサーがイヤリングにいたり、
To match my new outfit, Robosa are on my earrings,
新しい丸メガネは...
The new round glasses are...
ちょっとクールで装飾品もいっぱいついてるし、
A bit cool with lots of accessories,
何よりこのでっかいお団子...
And above all, these big buns...
かわちいでしょ！
Are cute, right!
もふもふもふもふ。
Mofu mofu mofu mofu.
僕、毛量多いの大好き。
I love having lots of hair.
ふふふ。ね。
Fufufu. Right?
え、このもふもふも可愛いよね。
Eh, this fluff is also cute, isn't it?
これ脱げるのかって？えー。
Can I take this off? Eh...
だって指だってまだちゃんと見れてないもんね。
Because we haven't seen my fingers properly yet.
脱げちゃうのかな？後で。
Will I take it off? Later.
あはは。後でお楽しみにしといてください。
Hahaha. Please look forward to it later.
はい。というわけで、え。
Yes. So, uh.
でもライブ以来だよ。COLORIZE衣装着たの。
But it's been since the live. Wearing the COLORIZE outfit.
カッコよかったでしょう？ギャル。
It was cool, wasn't it? Gal.
ね、めちゃめちゃ映えてたよね。うん。
Right, it looked really great. Yeah.
燃えちゃっかファイアーもね。
"Moecchakka Fire" too.
もう早くね、エリザベスが3Dモデル出ること、僕待ってるから。
I'm waiting for Elizabeth's 3D model to come out soon.
ベース！
Bass!
でも一緒に歌えてすごい楽しかった。
But it was so much fun singing together.
ありがとね、みんな。
Thank you, everyone.
はい。そして踊とシャンティと空も歌いましたけれども、
Yes. And I sang "Odo", "Shanti", and "Sora", too.
爆上げカッコよすぎロボ子さ。
High-tension, cool Roboco-san.
うん。一定数いますからね。
Yeah. There's a certain number of you.
ロボ子の低音が大好きすぎる民たち。
The people who love Roboco's low voice too much.
うん。いつもありがとう。
Yeah. Thank you as always.
すごい嬉しい。僕も気持ちよく歌えました。
I'm so happy. I could sing comfortably too.
あ、ところで。ステージがなんか進化して、
Ah, by the way. The stage has evolved somehow.
ドラゴン君が生まれてたの気づきました？
Did you notice the dragon-kun was born?
こいつ、どっから来たんや、お前ね。
This guy, where did you come from?
ロボ子食われちゃいそうだよね。
It looks like it's going to eat Roboco-san.
あはは。一回ロボ子をドラゴンの口の中に入れてみようかなって、
Hahaha. I thought about putting me in the dragon's mouth once,
ちょっと悩んだ。
I pondered it for a bit.
でも入れなかった。僕えらい。
But I didn't. I'm a good girl.
わー。あいつの上に乗らなすぎだろ。うん。
Whoa. I'm not riding on top of him at all. Yeah.
というわけでですね、
So, anyway,
もう次の歌も歌いたいんですけれども、
I want to sing the next song soon, but...
せっかくね、この衣装なので、
Since I'm in this outfit,
なんかゲストの中にめっちゃシナジーある奴がいるらしいんですよ。
It seems there's someone among the guests who has a lot of synergy.
歌っちゃおうかなー。
Should I sing together?
ね、ドラゴン君、歌いたいよね。
Right, Dragon-kun? You want to sing, don't you?
ね。
Right?
「歌いたい」
DRAGON: "I want to sing."
って言ってる気がするんで。
I feel like he's saying that.
じゃあ早速呼んでいきましょう。
So, let's call them out right away.
み、み、緑ー！
Mi- Mi- Midori!
ロボ子、久しぶり。お誕生日おめでとう！
Roboco, it's been a while. Happy birthday!
りゅーちゃん、ありがとう！ね、見て見て、新衣装！
Ryu-chan, thank you! Hey, look, look, my new outfit!
めっちゃ可愛い。めっちゃ可愛い。
It's so cute. So cute.
一緒に「いーあるふぁんくらぶ」歌おう！
Let's sing "Yi Er Fanclub" together!
いいよ。
Sure.
いーあるふぁんくらぶ
Yi Er Fanclub
う、は！
Uhh, ha!
神戸 中央区 元町。
Kobe, Chuo-ku, Motomachi.
駅前 今日から ドキドキ ニーハオ講座。
In front of the station, from today, an exciting Ni-Hao class.
大人 中高生 おばちゃんに。
Adults, students, and housewives.
「こんにちは」
"Hello."
ダメダメ ここでは あなたも 「ニーハオ」。
No, no, here, you too are "Ni-Hao".
マジでテキスト三ページ。
Seriously, page three of the textbook.
もっかい
One more time.
ここはとにかく羞恥に勝つぞ 一万三千の月謝は
Anyway, I'll conquer my shyness here. The 13,000 yen tuition...
(安くない)
(...isn't cheap!)
はーはーおじいさん ごきげんいかが
Ha-ha, old man, how are you doing?
おかあさん おうまさん ここはどこ きみはだれ
Mother, horse, where is this, who are you?
(先生)
(Teacher!)
だいすきなわん・りー・ほんさんに
To the Wang Leehom I love so much...
だいすきだって言うため
...just to say 'I love you.'
ハイハイチャイナ ちょちょ夢心地 いーあるふぁんくらぶ
Hi-Hi China, a little dreamlike, Yi-Er Fanclub.
だんだんきみと同じ言葉が 使えるね
Gradually, I can use the same words as you.
ウォーアイニー 言えるかな
Can I say 'Wo Ai Ni'?
ねえ見て りゅうちゃん 龍
Look, Ryu-chan! A dragon!
そこで知り合った女子高生ミカちゃん 曰く台湾ででちゃのコンサート
Mika-chan, the high school girl I met there, says there's a Jay Chou concert in Taiwan.
それは行かなきゃだめだ
I absolutely have to go to that.
ところでミカちゃん しれっと言ってるけど 海外だよ
By the way, Mika-chan, you say it so casually, but it's overseas.
マジでエンジンかかってんなミカちゃん ここはとにかく便乗して頑張るか
Mika-chan is really revved up. I guess I'll just jump on the bandwagon and do my best.
六万数千の旅費も
The 60,000-plus yen travel expenses...
(安くない)
(...aren't cheap!)
それでは再見(ツァイチェン) バイト探さなきゃ
Well then, zaijian! I have to look for a part-time job.
すみません おじょうさん チュウチェ ひとつ いくらでしょう
Excuse me, young lady, how much is one xiaolongbao?
天国のレスリー・チャンに
To Leslie Cheung in heaven...
おやすみなさいって言うため
...just to say 'goodnight.'
ハイハイチャイナ ちょちょ夢心地 いーあるふぁんくらぶ
Hi-Hi China, a little dreamlike, Yi-Er Fanclub.
だんだんきみの伝えたい気持ちが わかってく
Gradually, I'm understanding the feelings you want to convey.
憧れて 夢中になって
Yearning, becoming absorbed...
一ヶ月 二ヶ月 半年過ぎた
One month, two months, half a year has passed.
リア友は 少し減ったけど
My real-life friends have decreased a bit, but...
それもしかたないや
...that can't be helped.
ハイハイチャイナ ちょちょ夢心地 いーあるふぁんくらぶ
Hi-Hi China, a little dreamlike, Yi-Er Fanclub.
だんだんきみと同じ言葉が 使えるね
Gradually, I can use the same words as you.
ハイハイチャイナ ちょちょ夢心地 いーあるふぁんくらぶ
Hi-Hi China, a little dreamlike, Yi-Er Fanclub.
だんだんきみの伝えたい気持ちが わかってく
Gradually, I'm understanding the feelings you want to convey.
ウォーアイニー 言わせてよ
Let me say 'Wo Ai Ni.'
ウォーアイニー 言えるかな
Can I say 'Wo Ai Ni'?
ウォーアイニー
Wo Ai Ni.
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
うわあ！びっくりした！ありがとう！
Whoa! You startled me! Thank you!
呼び方やめてね！
Stop calling me that!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう ありがとう ありがとう
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
素敵
Lovely.
え？素敵じゃない あなた
Eh? Aren't you lovely yourself?
どこが素敵？
Where am I lovely?
もちろん 太もも
Of course, the thighs.
ねえ 全部とかじゃないの
Hey, not just a part of me?
もちろん 太ももフェチなの
Of course. I'm a thigh fetishist.
太もも好き
I like thighs.
どのへん？太もも
Which part? The thighs?
え、エッチだから
Eh, because they're sexy.
ねえ！
Hey!
僕、大好きそういうの ちょっと露出してるの ちょっとだけ
I love that kind of thing. Just a little exposure, just a bit.
アハハ！
Ahaha!
素敵じゃないですか
Isn't it wonderful?
いいよね！
It's good, isn't it!
でもあなたもね
But you too...
あ、僕ここ好き
Ah, I like this part.
このここ！
This part right here!
お揃いです
It's matching.
ここフェチ フェチズム
Here, a fetish, fetishism.
あー たまんねえ
Ah, I can't get enough.
たまんねえ
Can't get enough.
最高だ
It's the best.
人のこと言えない
Can't talk about others.
もうお互いそういう絡みしかできない
We can only interact like this now.
やばい 長年の適当な絡みになっちまってよ
Oh no, it's become a long-standing pattern of random interactions.
適当な緑仙です
I'm the random Ryushen.
はい 緑仙が来てくれました！
Yes, Ryushen has come!
来ましたー
I'm here!
ぴったりでしょ 今回
It's a perfect fit this time, right?
ねえ もう呼びたくて呼びたくて仕方なかった
I just wanted to call you so badly.
嬉しい
I'm happy.
なに？かっこいいポーズとか
What? A cool pose or something?
歌えたのがね、まず嬉しいよ
First of all, I'm happy we could sing.
え、そうだよね
Eh, that's true.
確かに 歌ったことないね
Indeed, we haven't sung together.
そうなんです 歌ったことなかったから
That's right, we hadn't sung together.
なにこれ？
What is this?
わかんない なんか喋りながらポーズしておこうかなと思って
I don't know. I thought I'd strike a pose while talking.
待て
Wait.
みんな落ち着け 落ち着いて
Everyone calm down, calm down.
写真を撮っていい 勝手に
You can take photos. Freely.
いい感じで撮っていい
You can take them in a good way.
うん 勝手に スクショを撮って
Yeah, freely take screenshots.
タグを付けて 投稿してほしい
I want you to tag them and post them.
ハッシュタグは何ですか？
What's the hashtag?
ハッシュタグは そんなこと、ここを見ればわかるだろ
The hashtag... you can tell by looking here.
端折らないでよ！
Don't cut corners!
えー 長年だと手抜くんすか？
Eh? You're being lazy since we've known each other for long?
うそ そんなことないです
No, that's not true.
なんすか その途中の...
What was that in the middle...
ん？
Hmm?
途中の... あ、上指さして
In the middle... ah, pointing up.
んー だって あなたの名前って 緑仙じゃないですか
Hmm? Because your name is Ryushen, isn't it?
龍、あ、龍...
Ryuu... ah, Ryuu...
あ、龍、お、龍、ほらほら龍、龍、龍。
Ah, Ryuu... oh, Ryuu... look, look, Ryuu, Ryuu, Ryuu.
「いてて」ってなっちゃった。
I ended up saying, "Ouch."
だって、だってあそこ僕に任されたんだもん。
Because, because I was entrusted with that part.
で、しかもさ僕のこと、「龍ちゃん」って呼んでるよね？
And besides, you're calling me "Ryuu-chan," aren't you?
うん、龍ちゃん。
Yeah, Ryuu-chan.
今日。
Today.
でも普段は、「翠」とか言うんですよ。
But usually, you say things like "Midori."
えへへ。
Ehehe.
今日だけ「龍ちゃん！」とか言って。
Only today, you're like, "Ryuu-chan!"
龍ちゃ～ん！
Ryuu-chaaan!
やべぇ、なんか幼馴染面で、近寄ってきたのと思って。
Oh man, I thought you were approaching me
with that childhood friend vibe.
すごいドキドキしてます。
My heart is racing.
え、本当？可愛くぶっちゃった。
Oh, really? I was acting a bit cute.
可愛い、ずーっと可愛いこれ。
Cute, you're always cute.
え、可愛いでしょ？
Right? I'm cute, aren't I?
うん、可愛い。
Yeah, cute.
龍ちゃん見て見て。
Ryuu-chan, look, look!
え、可愛い。
Oh, cute.
きちゃった。
I've arrived.
ねぇみんな、僕の分も褒めてあげてください。
Hey everyone, please praise me too.
僕はあまり褒めないので。
Since she doesn't praise me much.
えー。褒めろよ。
Eh? Praise me!
いや可愛い、本当に可愛い。
No, you're cute, really cute.
おい龍ちゃん、あざといポーズしろ。
Hey Ryuu-chan, do a calculate-ly cute pose.
えー、一緒にしよう。
Eh? Let's do it together.
しよう。
Let's.
え、可愛い。きゅるん。
Oh, cute. Kyurun!
きゅるん。
Kyurun!
かっこいい、可愛い。最高やないの。
Cool and cute. Isn't it the best?
いいじゃないですか。
It's good, isn't it?
え、なんかポーズしようよ。希望あれば。
Eh, let's do a pose. If you have a request...
なんなりと。
...anything.
パンチ？
Punch?
パンチ？パンチ？
Punch? Punch?
でもね、クソ雑魚パンチしたもんね、我々一緒に。
But we did that crappy weak punch together, didn't we?
超つよパンチ！
Super strong punch!
超つよパンチ？
Super strong punch?
かかってこいよ。
Bring it on!
かかってこいよ。おお、最高。
Bring it on! Oh, awesome.
強そう。
Looks strong.
本当に強そうになっちゃった。
You really ended up looking strong.
なんか撃退したいリプライとかあったらね、これ使っても。
If there's any reply you want to repel,
you could use this.
ね、使ってこらそう。
Yeah, let's use it and teach them a lesson.
かかってこい、倒します。
Bring it on! We'll take you down.
かかってこい、かかってこい。
Bring it on, bring it on!
クソリプ、全部倒します。
Crappy replies, we'll defeat them all.
え、見て、龍ちゃん好きそう。
Oh, look! Ryuu-chan seems to like this.
可愛い、マジで可愛い、本当に。
Cute! Seriously cute, really.
好きそう。素敵。
Looks like it. Lovely.
いいね。ちょっとポーズはさておき素敵よ。
Nice. Poses aside, you're lovely.
やった。ポーズも褒めて。
Yay! Praise the pose too.
うん、適当なポーズも褒めて。
Yeah, praise the random poses too.
めちゃくちゃいい感じでしょ？強そう。
Looks great, right? Strong.
おーおー。
Oh, oh!
わー！
Waa!
いくつか可愛い。え、止まんないよもう、褒め出したら。
So many "cutes." I can't stop once I start praising.
やばい、やばい、やばい。
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
そんな、嬉しい。
I'm so happy.
本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much, truly.
今日呼んでよかった。
I'm glad I invited you today.
マジで呼んでくれてありがとう。
Seriously, thank you for inviting me.
ありがたありがた。
Thanks, thanks.
今日はね、まだ...
Today, there's still...
自分、締めるの下手かもと思って。
I was thinking maybe I'm bad at wrapping things up.
頑張ってね。頑張ってね。
Good luck! Good luck!
頑張るね。
I'll do my best.
閉廷散会！あいつマジで本当に雑なんだよ。
Court adjourned! That guy is seriously so blunt.
はい、というわけで、翠でした。
Alright, so that was Midori.
龍ちゃんでも何でも呼んであげてください。
Please call him Ryuu-chan or whatever you like.
じゃ、ロボ子、次は頑張りますんで、うー、パンチ！
Well then, Roboco is going to do her best next, so...
Woo, punch!
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは溶けそうなチャイナ
The rest is a melting China
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは弾けるチャイナ
The rest is a popping China
春茶、誕生日おめでとう！
Harucha, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
春茶、バーチャルの世界へようこそ！
Harucha, welcome to the virtual world!
影も真っ黒になっちゃった。
Even my shadow has turned jet black.
僕も真っ黒。
I'm jet black too.
それじゃ、マイクマイク...行ってきます！
Well then, mic, mic... here I go!
ウォーアイニー
Wo ai ni
君にウォーアイニー
I love you (Wo ai ni)
ウォーアイニー
Wo ai ni
あなたに
To you
意外と簡単に落ちる
Falling surprisingly easily
ウォーアイニー
Wo ai ni
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは溶けそうなチャイナ
The rest is a melting China
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは弾けるチャイナ
The rest is a popping China
前場に悶え
Writhing at the opening
君にウォーアイニー
I love you (Wo ai ni)
ウォーアイニー
Wo ai ni
ひそかに
Secretly
中途の公開に終わる
Ending in mid-way exposure
ウォーアイニー
Wo ai ni
そんなやつやめちゃいな
Just quit with that kind of guy
チャイナ
China
チャイナアドバイス
China Advice
もう私の虜にね
Be captivated by me now
チャイナ
China
チャイナアドバイス
China Advice
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは溶けそうなチャイナ
The rest is a melting China
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは弾けるチャイナ
The rest is a popping China
徐々に限界に潜む
Gradually lurking at the limit
ウォーアイニー
Wo ai ni
そう曖昧に
So ambiguously
大人の全開に挑む
Challenging the adult's full blast
ウォーアイニー
Wo ai ni
ねえそろそろやめちゃいな
Hey, isn't it time to quit?
チャイナ
China
チャイナアドバイス
China Advice
いい加減に大人にな
Grow up already
チャイナ
China
チャイナアドバイス
China Advice
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは溶けそうなチャイナ
The rest is a melting China
I wanna do it do it yeah
あとは弾けるチャイナ
The rest is a popping China
そんなやつやめちゃいな
Just quit with that kind of guy
チャイナ
China
チャイナアドバイス
China Advice
アドバイス　もっと私に夢中になって
advice, be more obsessed with me.
チャイナ　チャイナ　チャイナ　チャイナアドバイス
China, China, China, China Advice.
さあ　今手を出してたまにはさ
Come on, reach out your hand once in a while,
チャイナ　チャイナ　チャイナ　チャイナアドバイス
China, China, China, China Advice.
あぁ　私をもう虜にして
Ah, just make me your captive already.
チャイナ　チャイナ　チャイナ　チャイナアドバイス
China, China, China, China Advice.
チャイナ　チャイナ　チャイナ　さぁ　チャイナアドバイス
China, China, China, come on, China Advice.
ハルちゃーん！嬉しい一緒に歌えて！
Haru-chaaan! I'm so happy to sing with you!
楽しかった！
That was fun!
楽しかった！ありがとう！
It was fun! Thank you!
ありがとう、こちらこそ。
Thank you, likewise.
ハルちゃんそこから出れないの？今日。
Haru-chan, you can't come out of there today?
そう。ここが家。
Yeah. This is my home.
あははは！すごいよね、これね。
Ahahaha! This is amazing, isn't it?
え、すごいよね。
Yeah, it's amazing.
というわけで、今日はハルちゃんがゲストに来てくれました！
Anyway, today Haru-chan has come as a guest!
こんにちは。ハルちゃんです。ハルチャです。
Hello. I'm Haru-chan. I'm Hal-cha.
ハルちゃんがさ、すごい多分みんなも「えっ、そこ接点あるの？」って多分めっちゃ思われると思うよね。
Haru-chan, I think everyone's probably thinking,
"Wait, they have a connection?"
一回だけね、ポストとかでね、スター... お土産ね。
Just once, in a post, a star... A souvenir.
そう、お土産をね、あげたの。
Right, I gave you a souvenir.
そう、もらった。
Yeah, I received it.
そう、で、実はハルちゃんからも僕は、お土産をもらってる。
Right, and actually, I received a souvenir
from Haru-chan too.
確かあげたわ。
I definitely gave you one.
そう。でもそれはポストしてない。
Yeah. But I haven't posted about that.
あはは。そう、なんのかんのね、結構ね、遊んでたりもしたからね。
Ahaha. Yeah, one way or another, we've
hung out quite a bit.
今回はお呼びしました。どうでしたか？
So I invited her this time. How was it?
どうでしたか？え、私に聞いてる今？
How was it? Wait, are you asking me now?
え、みんなに聞いてる。
No, I'm asking everyone.
あ、みんなに。あははは。
Oh, everyone. Ahahaha.
え、でもどうだった？一緒に歌って。
But how was it for you? Singing together.
え、超楽しかった。
It was super fun.
嬉しい！僕も楽しかった。
I'm happy! I had fun too.
ね、初めて歌ってさ、歌ったよね。
Right, it was the first time we sang together,
isn't it?
歌ったよ。そうだよね、歌った。
We did. That's right, we sang.
そう。こういう場所でね。
Yeah. In a place like this.
そうだよね。だってさ、声色が結構さ、近いからさ、絶対これ似合うやんと思って、今回はチャイナアドバイス呼びました。
Right. Because our voices are quite similar, I
thought this would definitely suit us,
so I invited her for 'China Advice'.
ロボ子が決めたの。
I decided on it.
あ、そうなんだ。え、高性能でしょ？すごい、高性能。
Oh, really? Wow, you're high-spec, aren't you?
Amazing, high-spec.
さすが！
As expected!
ハルちゃんがさ、珍しいんだよ。僕のこと「ロボ子」って呼ぶの。
Haru-chan, it's rare, you know. You calling
me "Roboco".
え、そうなの？
Oh, really?
そう。珍しいんだよ。
Yeah. It's rare.
あんまりいないの？マジで。
There aren't many people who do? Seriously?
さっき聞いてびっくりした。
I was surprised when I heard it earlier.
もうナチュラルにずっとロボ子なの。
I've just been naturally calling you Roboco
all along.
そう、ずっとロボ子。
Yeah, always Roboco.
え、逆に何？何が多い？
Wait, then what? What do most people call you?
えー、ロボ子ちゃんとか、ロボやん、先輩とか。
Umm, Roboco-chan, Roboyan, Senpai, and so on.
あぁ、ね。それはちょっとよくわかんない。先輩なの？ロボ子。
Ah, I see. I don't really get that.
Are you a senpai, Roboco?
え、そう、先輩なんだよ、一応。
Yeah, well, I am a senpai, technically.
えぇ！？
What!?
え、ねぇ、なんか、これ本当やりたかったけどできなくて忘れてた。ハート作ります！
Hey, I really wanted to do this but couldn't
and forgot. Let's make a heart!
ハート！
Heart!
え、あ、行けそうじゃない？
Oh, doesn't it look like it'll work?
あ、みんな、みんな写真撮って！みんな写真撮って！
Ah, everyone, everyone take a picture!
Everyone take a picture!
でもいい感じやん。
But it looks good.
え、可愛い。
Oh, it's cute.
え、どう？これ、新衣装なんですけれど。超可愛いと思います。
Hey, how is it? This is my new outfit.
I think it's super cute.
え、ハルちゃん的におすすめのポーズとかあったら撮っちゃうんだけど。
Hey, if you have a recommended pose,
Haru-chan, I'll take it.
え、ちょっとあれやってよ、上目遣い。
Umm, do that one, the upturned eyes.
上目遣い？
Upturned eyes?
カメラ向いて。可愛い可愛い。
Look at the camera. Cute, cute.
ハルちゃん、ハルちゃん。いっぱい遊んで。
Haru-chan, Haru-chan. Play with me lots.
可愛い。いっぱい遊ぼう。
Cute. Let's play lots.
でも手はごついんだよね。
But the hands are rugged, aren't they?
ね、そう。めちゃめちゃかっこいい。見て。
Yeah, they are. They're super cool. Look.
え、でも好きでしょ？こういうの。
Hey, but you like this kind of thing, right?
うん、いいよ。ごつい。かっこいい。
Yeah, I do. Rugged. Cool.
これめっちゃ高い。
These were really expensive.
高いんだ。おー、そう。良さそう。
They're expensive? Oh, I see. They look good.
めっちゃ高い。多分。パパが作ってくれた。
Super expensive. Probably.
Papa made them for me.
パパもすごいな。
Your papa is amazing too.
パパもすごいな。え、お団子もさ、超可愛くない？
Papa is amazing too.
Hey, aren't the buns super cute too?
え、お団子可愛いでしょう。
The buns are definitely cute.
見て。ほら。毛量がめちゃめちゃあるんです、ロボ子。
Look. See? Roboco has a ton of hair volume.
後ろから見るとすごいね。
Looking from the back, it's impressive.
ボボボボボボボム。
Vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom boom.
全部可愛い。
Everything is cute.
やった！オールパーフェクトじゃん。
Yay! It's all perfect then.
パーフェクト。
Perfect.
ハルちゃんこれ途中でやってたの気づいた？これ。歌ってる最中。
Haru-chan, did you notice me doing this in the
middle? This. While singing.
これ？歌ってる時？やってたわ。気づいた気づいた。
This? While singing? You were doing it.
I noticed, I noticed.
なんかやってたよね。こっち見てやってたよね。しかも。
You were doing something, right? You were looking
this way while doing it. On top of that.
気づけー！ってドヤ顔でやってた。
I was doing it with a smug face,
like "Notice me!"
気づいた気づいた。
I noticed, I noticed.
はー。というわけで。
Sigh. Anyway.
ロボ子おめでとう、本当に。
Roboco, congratulations, seriously.
ハルちゃん、ありがとう。え、なんかすごいあれだね。
Haru-chan, thank you. Wait, it's really
something, isn't it?
え、何何？
Huh, what what?
なんかすごい、本当におめでとうってすごいめちゃ丁寧に行ってくれるからさ、ありがたいなと思って。
It's just, you said "Congratulations" so
very politely, so I thought it was really kind.
おめでたいんだもの、だって。
Well, it is a celebratory occasion, after all.
え、嬉しい、ありがとう！
Oh, I'm happy, thank you!
次も。
Next too.
うん。まだ早いか。
Yeah. Is it too early yet?
いいよ。大丈夫か。
It's fine. Will it be okay?
まだね、いっぱいあると思うからね、頑張って。
Since I think there's still plenty more to
come, do your best.
頑張る。ハルちゃんじゃあ応援してね。
I will. Haru-chan, please root for me then.
応援する。見てるね。
I will. I'll be watching.
見てて。ありがとう。バイバイ！
Watch me. Thank you. Bye bye!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
バイバイハルちゃん！またね！
Bye bye Haru-chan! See you!
おめでとバイバイ！
Congrats, bye bye!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
ハルちゃんて結構マイペースなんですよ。
Haru-chan is quite the "my-pace" person.
許婚っきゅん
Inazukkyun
どいつもこいつもなんだかやっぱ能天気
Everyone's somehow carefree after all
気に食わぬあの子も悩みはきっとあるでしょう
Even that girl I don't like must have worries
たったれ半端な憂鬱ともう群れ同じ
Just half-baked melancholy, just another one in the herd
頭の中はぐちゃぐちゃさ
Inside my head is a mess
どんまい平気、意気地がないのはお互い様
Don't mind, it's okay, we're both spineless
行けない行けない事柄なんてないからさ
Because there's no such thing as "I can't do it"
嫌気が差すじゃんけんぽんでさあおゆき
Sick of it, rock-paper-scissors, now go
有頂天爆破で天に召されてく
Ascending to heaven with an ecstatic blast
君はもうハイスピードだな
You're already at high speed
ぐっちゃぐちゃお似合いだね
A complete mess, it suits you
はっちゃけてめちゃなドラマ
Burst out with a reckless drama
お空が鳴るよ
The sky is roaring
いいなずきゅん　アイラブユーなのさ
Inazukyun, I love you, you see
四六時中　愛を頂戴
Give me your love 24/7
待っていちかばちきゅん　アイアイアイワナロッキュー
Wait, all-or-nothing kyun, I-I-I wanna rock you
2分の1じゃもの足りない
Half isn't enough
それでも結局見えないあいつの胸の内
But in the end, I can't see what's in his heart
お邪魔な世間の口出しもいらないから
I don't need the meddling of the bothersome public
先輩後輩、ヤンキーちゃんキー関係ない
Seniors, juniors, delinquents, doesn't matter
いざ尋常に勝負
Now, let's fight fairly
君がもしもその気なら
If you're up for it
ボーイミーツガールが始まりそうならさ
If boy-meets-girl is about to start
待った見ぬ技繰り出す
Hold on, unleashing an unseen move
僕らてんやわんやスイートだな
We're in a sweet hectic mess
へっちゃら顔同じだね
A nonchalant face, we're the same
へっちゃらでメチャな修羅場
Nonchalantly in a reckless mayhem
お空が鳴るよ
The sky is roaring
意味深な抱擁　曖昧な愛より直情
A meaningful hug, more direct than vague love
四の五の言わず察して頂戴
Stop making excuses and just sense it
待っていちびるな電中　鼻血ボーンさ
Wait, don't get cocky on the phone, nosebleed blast
自分の意思はどうなんだい
How about your own will?
いいなずきゅん　アイラブユーなのさ
Inazukyun, I love you, you see
四六時中　愛を頂戴
Give me your love 24/7
待っていちかばちきゅん　アイアイアイワナロッキュー
Wait, all-or-nothing kyun, I-I-I wanna rock you
2分の1じゃ物足りない
Half isn't enough
こんなんじゃ知らない　会いたいかも知れん
I don't know it like this, I might want to see you
毎晩きっと全然足りないや
Every night is surely not enough at all
空前絶後で天使占う
Unprecedented, predicting an angel
変愛無常めっちょ回転
Metamorphosis love, rotating like crazy
はい、というわけで、いいなずきゅんでしたー！どうでしたかー？
Okay, so that was Inazukyun! How was it?
え、シルエットのさ、ここかっこよくなかった？ポン、ポンってしてんの。
Hey, wasn't this silhouette part cool? The "pom, pom" movement.
結構お気に入りポイントです。
It's a favorite point of mine.
はい、どうだった？可愛いでしょ、改めて新衣装。
Yes, how was it? It's cute, right? My new outfit once again.
ねー、緑とも春ちゃんともね、歌えて嬉しい！
Right? I'm happy to be able to sing with Midori and Haru-chan!
まさかの、「えー」って思ってる人が出てもね、めっちゃ多かったと思うんだけど、お呼びしました、今回は。
Even if many people thought "Eh!?", I invited them this time.
嬉しいです。
I'm happy.
さあ、というわけで、もう結構歌ったねー。うん。
Well, anyway, we've sung quite a lot, haven't we? Yeah.
なんか、そろそろウズウズしてる人たちがいっぱいいる気がするなー。
I feel like there are many people who are starting to get restless now.
ウズ、ウズ、ウズ、ウズ、ウズ、ウズ。僕が一番ウズウズしてる。
Restless, restless, restless... I'm the most restless one.
はい、というわけで、待ちきれないので、ご紹介したいと思います。
Okay, so I can't wait anymore, so I'd like to introduce it.
誕生日といえば！
Speaking of birthdays...
誕生日グッズ！今回の誕生日グッズはこちら！
Birthday merchandise! Here's the birthday merchandise for this time!
はい、久しぶりにタペストリーを出します。
Yes, I'm releasing a tapestry after a long time.
まず一つ目、B2タペストリー。
First one, the B2 tapestry.
こちらイラストはね、とってもクールな僕なんですけれども、SHAGAMU先生に書いていただきました。
This illustration is a very cool me, drawn by SHAGAMU-sensei.
え、あ、これ、龍違いとかやめてね。
Hey, ah, don't confuse the dragons.
龍！お前も好きだし、お前も好きだぞ。みんな愛してる。龍です。
Dragon! I like you, and I like you too. I love everyone. It's a dragon.
めっちゃかっこいいよね。
It's really cool, isn't it?
強そうな龍と、強そうな僕。かっこいいでしょ。
A strong-looking dragon and a strong-looking me. Cool, right?
そして二つ目は、なんと！お腹いっぱい食べてね餃子皿！
And the second one is, wow! An "eat your fill" gyoza plate!
なんと、こちらロボ子先生が書いてくれました。
Surprisingly, Roboco-sensei (me) drew this.
えー、見てなんか、すっごいもう、いっぱい食べられそうでしょ。
Look, it looks like you can eat a lot from it, right?
いっぱい食べる気満々の、沼にはまってるロボ子とロボサ、めちゃめちゃ可愛いでしょ？
Roboco and Robosa, looking so eager to eat and stuck in a bowl, aren't they adorable?
このお皿を使って、いっぱいね、餃子なり何なり食べてください。
Please use this plate to eat lots of gyoza or whatever you like.
お腹いっぱいになると幸せになれるのでね。
Being full makes you happy, you know.
はい。そして次は、
Yes. And next...
ご飯を​食べたら​喉も​乾く、​ちあーず！​グラスですね。
When you eat, you get thirsty. It's the Cheers! Glass.
ちあーず！グラス
Cheers! Glass
ビール入れてもいいし、お茶入れたっていいし、ジュース入れたっていい。美味しいもの飲んでいきましょう。
You can put beer in it, or tea, or juice. Let's drink something delicious.
こちらもなんとロボ子先生が描いてくれました、高性能なボクだ。可愛すぎる。
Roboco-sensei drew this one too! It's the high-performance me. So cute.
こんなウインクされたら、いっぱい飲んだっていいですからね。
If you get a wink like this, it's okay to drink a lot.
ぜひ、ご飯と飲み物、食卓にお使いくださいまし。
Please use them for your meals and drinks at the table.
今度ボクも配信で使ってみようと思うので、ぜひチェックしてみてください。
I'm thinking of using it in a stream sometime, so please check it out.
そしてまだまだあります。こちら、ドン！
And there's still more. Here, bam!
おすわりぬいぐるみ 料理対決衣装ver.
Sitting Plushie: Cooking Battle Outfit ver.
はい、ボクの大好きなぬいぐるみ！本日も可愛いものができました。
Yes, my favorite plushie! Another cute one was made today.
見て、お座りしてんの、今回のお座りぬいぐるみ。ちゃんとロボサもここにいますよ。
Look, it's sitting! This time it's a sitting plushie. Robosa is right here too.
今回はね、お座りのぬいぐるみなので、このままお部屋に飾ってもいいし、お出かけにも一緒に写真撮りやすいのかなと思います。
Since it's a sitting plushie, you can display it in your room as is, or take it out to easily snap photos together.
いっぱい色んなところに連れて行ってあげてください。
Please take it to many different places.
大切にしてね。失くさないでね。置いて行かないでね。たくさん買ったっていいんだからね。
Take good care of it. Don't lose it. Don't leave it behind. You can buy as many as you want!
そして、ボイスも出ます。
And, there's a voice pack too.
シチュエーションボイス 『ぼく vs りゅう』
Situation Voice: 'Me vs. Dragon'
今回は、『ぼく vs りゅう』。
This time, it's 'Me vs. Dragon'.
マジ龍の名前刺さりまくらんのよ。緑だっていいし、龍だっていいし、ドラゴンくんだっていいし、ドラちゃんだっていい。
The dragon theme really resonates with me. Green is fine, Ryu is fine, Dragon-kun or Dra-chan, anything's fine.
何だっていい。いいよね。ね。
Anything works. It's nice, right? Yeah.
はい、キミに襲い掛かる龍に、可愛さ勝負を挑むボクのお話。
It's a story of me challenging a dragon that attacks you to a cuteness battle.
キュッ！はい。どんなお話かはぜひ買って聴いてみてください。
*Squeak!* Please buy it and listen to find out what kind of story it is.
さあ最後に、こちら。
Now finally, this.
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonuses
はい、今回のフルセット購入特典についてお話しします。
Yes, I'll talk about this time's full set purchase bonuses.
えーまず一つ目。数量限定版が今回はあります。
First off, we have a limited quantity edition this time.
数量限定版は、ボクの直筆サインと、箔押しの複製メッセージ入りのポストカードになります。
The limited quantity edition includes a postcard with my handwritten signature and a foil-stamped duplicate message.
今回はボクのこの配信が終わったと同時にカートがオープンしますので、そのタイミングでぜひ狙ってみてください。
The cart opens right after this stream ends, so please try to get it then.
スタートダッシュの準備はいいか？ぜひゲットしてくださいね。
Are you ready for the head start? Please get yours!
はい、もちろん通常版もあります。通常版はボクの直筆サインはないんですけど、箔押し入りのサインとメッセージのポストカードが付いてきますので、ぜひゲットしてください。
Of course, there's a standard edition too. It doesn't have the handwritten signature, but it comes with a foil-stamped signature and message postcard, so please get that one too.
そしてまだフルセット購入特典にはボイスが付きます。
And there's more—the full set bonus includes additional voices.
一つ目、『君と龍と夜の空』。こちらは販売ボイスの少し後の時間帯のお話で、なんと時間軸は続いております。
First one, 'You, the Dragon, and the Night Sky'. This is a story set shortly after the main voice pack; the timeline is actually connected.
販売ボイスは別に単体でも楽しめますけど、特典ボイスも合わせると、えっ、あの後の続きがあるの？って楽しめるので、ぜひ聴いてほしいです。
You can enjoy the main voice pack on its own, but with the bonus voice, you'll be like, 'Wait, there's a sequel?' so I definitely want you to hear it.
面白いよ。ふふ。
It's interesting. Hehe.
そしてなんと、今回は、ジャーン！
And surprisingly, this time... ta-da!
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PRカード HBD24-047 「ロボ子さん」
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PR Card HBD24-047 'Roboco-san'
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、2024年9月から発売がされたホロライブ公式カードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚付いてきます。
As a full set bonus for the Talent Premium Goods, you'll get one card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game, which launched in September 2024.
同梱するカードはホロライブプロダクション公式ショップで購入されたお客様のみの対象となります。
The included card is only for those who purchase through the Hololive Production Official Shop.
今回特典に付くのは、ゲームで1枚だけ使用でき、推しをアピールすることができるカード、『推しホロメンカード』です！
The bonus card this time is an 'Oshi Holomen Card', a card you can use only once per game to show off your favorite!
え、みんな欲しいっしょこれ。1枚、今しか買えない。ロボサーは買うべき。強いよ。ふふ。
Everyone wants this, right? It's just one card, and you can only get it now. Robosa, you should buy it. It's strong! Hehe.
はい、ということでカードの詳細や遊び方については、多分ボクから聞くよりホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームの公式ホームページで確認したほうが分かりやすいと思うので、ぜひチェックしてみてください。
So, for card details and how to play, it's probably easier to check the Hololive Official Card Game's official website than to hear it from me, so please take a look.
はい、同梱するカードは日本語版のみとなりますのでご了承ください。No English sorry. うん。
Please note that the included card is only in Japanese. No English, sorry. Yeah.
グッズのカートオープンはこの後配信終了後になりますので、みんな、待機して買ってね。いっぱい買ったっていい。ふふ。
The goods cart opens right after this stream, so everyone, please wait for it and buy. It's okay to buy a lot! Hehe.
そしてこの後はなんと...
And then, after this, would you believe it...
実は初めてのメインア...ア...ア...アンコールライブがあります！
Actually, there's going to be the first Main A... A... A... Encore Live!
お酒は飲んでも飲まれるな。
Drink alcohol, but don't let it drink you.
最近お酒飲んでない。ふふ。
I haven't been drinking lately. *Chuckles*
あー、アンコールとアルコール似てるんだわ。
Ah, "Encore" and "Alcohol" sound so similar.
はい、ということでなんと今回はね、アンコールライブがありますので
Yes, so believe it or not, there's an Encore Live this time.
アンコールライブはね、みんながずっと僕に歌って欲しそうだったあの曲を歌っちゃおうかなと思ってますので
For the Encore Live, I'm thinking of singing that song you've all wanted me to sing for so long.
楽しみにしててくださーい！
Please look forward to it!
なんかせっかくだからね、写真撮影会とかね
Since we're here, I'm thinking of doing a photo session and stuff.
ロボサーと密な空間でいっぱい見せちゃおうかなって思ってます
I want to show you a lot of things in a close-up setting with the Robosa.
メンバーのプレゼントもありがとうね、みんな。ぜひ見ててください
Thank you everyone for the member presents too. Please stay tuned.
はい、ということで
Yes, so...
ロボサー、早いけど、次が最後の曲になっちゃうみたいです
Robosa, it's early, but it seems like the next one will be the last song.
僕はもう９歳。
I'm already 9 years old.
９歳になったロボ子、ここまで成長を見届けてくれてありがとうね
Now that I've turned 9, thank you for watching over my growth until now.
これからもまだまだ僕は成長していくので
I'm going to keep growing even more from now on.
一緒に末長く楽しんでいきましょう
So let's enjoy our time together for many years to come.
最後の曲は、始めにチラッと言ったけど
For the last song, as I mentioned briefly at the start...
ドラゴンくんに乗りたいな！
I want to ride on the dragon!
一緒に頑張ってくれる？ねぇ、ドラゴンくん
Will you work hard with me? Right, Dragon-kun?
DAN DAN 心魅かれてく
DAN DAN, my heart is being captivated
その眩しい笑顔に
By that dazzling smile of yours
果てない暗闇から飛び出そう
Let's fly out from the endless darkness
Hold my hand
君と出逢ったとき
When I first met you
子供の頃 大切に想っていた
I remembered the place I cherished
場所を思い出したんだ
Back when I was a child
僕と踊ってくれないか
Won't you dance with me?
光と影の Winding Road
On this winding road of light and shadow
今でも あいつに夢中なの？
Are you still crazy about that guy?
少しだけ 振り向きたくなるような 時もあるけど
There are times when I feel like looking back just a little
愛と勇気と誇りを持って闘うよ
But I'll fight with love, courage, and pride
DAN DAN 心魅かれてく
DAN DAN, my heart is being captivated
この星の希望のかけら
By the fragments of hope on this planet
きっと誰もが 永遠を手に入れたい
I'm sure everyone wants to grasp eternity
全然気にしないふりしても
Even if I pretend not to care at all
ほら君に恋してる
See, I'm in love with you
果てない暗闇から飛び出そう
Let's fly out from the endless darkness
Hold your hand
怒った顔も疲れてる君も好きだけど
I like your angry face and even when you're tired
あんなに飛ばして生きて大丈夫かなと思う
But I wonder if it's okay for you to live life so fast
僕は 何気ない仕草に 振り回されてる
I'm being tossed around by your casual gestures
sea side blue
In the seaside blue
それでも あいつに夢中なの？
And yet, are you still crazy about that guy?
もっと聞きたいことがあったのに
Even though there were more things I wanted to ask
二人の会話が 車の音に
Our conversation gets obstructed by the sound of cars
阻まれて通りに舞うよ
And dances away into the street
DAN DAN 心魅かれてく
DAN DAN, my heart is being captivated
自分でも不思議なんだけど
It's strange even to me
何かあるとすぐに 君に電話したくなる
But whenever something happens, I want to call you right away
全然気のないふりしても
Even if I pretend to have no interest at all
結局 君のこと見てる
In the end, I'm looking at you
果てない暗闇から飛び出そう
Let's fly out from the endless darkness
Hold my hand
結局君のことだけ見てた
In the end, I was only looking at you
海の彼方へ
To the other side of the sea,
飛び出そうよ Hold my hand
let's fly out together. Hold my hand
おっとっとっとっと...
Oops-a-daisy...
みんな
Everyone,
ロボサー
Robosa,
今日は見てくれてありがとう！
thank you for watching today!
この後はなんと！
And after this, guess what?
メンバー限定でも歌います！
I'll be singing in a members-only stream too!
遊びに来てね！
Come hang out!
グッズもめっちゃ可愛ちいから
The goods are super cute too,
ゲットしてくれよなー！
so please get them!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
なんか君も遅いね、ドラゴンくん。
You're a bit slow too, aren't you, Mr. Dragon?
Thank you watching♡
カッコいい新衣装お披露目！！
歌えてうれしい！！ロボさ、大好き♡
Thank you for watching♡
Cool new outfit reveal!!
I'm so happy I could sing!! I love you, Robosa♡
NEXT ➡ 鬼のうたげup 👹 アンコールライブ
NEXT ➡ Oni no Utage up 👹 Encore Live